Thank you for watching.
I don't know. I feel like I was suddenly put on a boat.
Not a boat, though.
We've landed.
Where is it?
They said it's uninhabited.
A deserted island?
It's uninhabited.
What the hell?
We're just thrown out here in the mountains. What is it?
Morning.
We had a cooking competition once.
When?
A year and a half ago
To be continued next time
You know how they punish you?
Well, well, well, of course I know.
Today, I'm going to ask you two to survive.
Try not to die.
Good luck.
Oh, no.
If you're not careful, you'll die.
No, that's what I meant.
Zero.
I mean, he's zero.
I mean, I can't even handle bugs or anything. Zero.
Well, well, well. I don't like it that much.
I grew up in a place like this.
Really?
This is where I grew up.
Okazaki this?
Yes. This is where I was raised. This is where I was raised.
I see.
That's good.
So you think you're ready?
You can do it.
You have first orders?
Survival order number one.
Use the tools you've been given and build a base.
Sword. Now.
So that's how it's going to be.
That's how it's gonna be.
Oh, no, Gellar.
But you're right. We need to build a stronghold.
Because if you get attacked by a beast...
I won't be able to come back.
The tools are over there.
Oh, really?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
What? This little? Tents?
Aren't there instructions for these things? Survival.
What?
We've already started?
Yes, sir.
Let's see what we've got here.
I think it's a tent, maybe.
Maybe.
A tent...
It's probably a... a sheet.
But, you know, tents aren't usually supposed to have these pillars or something like that.
What's this?
And this is the mysterious...
It's not a mystery.
These are stakes.
Stake it out.
This guy can't do anything.
What is this? It's a little hard to get a handle on this.
Survival knife.
Holy shit.
What do you use that for?
What do you do with it?
For cutting wood.
Cutter.
But...
Chopping wood?
Well, with our staff, I'm pretty sure they're just trying to trick us into thinking they're chopping wood.
They're trying to fool us, so I don't think some of them get it.
That's right.
That's great.
You want to open this up for me?
Okay.
Depending on how wide this is.
By the size of this one.
Do you have a tent like this? What's this?
I've never seen anything like it.
What's this?
Even if it's shaped like this, it's still a tent, right?
It's a deal.
Here we go. Open it.
Oh, but it is.
Well, it's spacious.
What's this?
What is it?
What does that mean?
What? - No, I don't know.
I don't know.
What do you think?
It's a sleeping bag, but...
Well, that sucks.
That sucks.
You and me, we'll put a car in the driveway and we'll come out here.We'll both get in the car and bring it here.
It's the only way.
Wait a minute.
I don't know what's right.
I got this.
We're gonna use this, too.
Yeah.
Right here in the middle.
It's kind of important.
Like this.
Whoa.
Oh, isn't that it?
Oh.
Tie the rope around the tree.
That's it.
And hang it here.
That's it, man.
That's it.
That's the one.
Wait, let me through first.
Let's go ahead.
Yeah, let's go ahead.
So, let's see.
I can do this.
I can do it.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I'm sorry.
I'm almost in trouble now.
I'm really, really, really sorry.
I don't know what I was gonna do.
I really was.
Right here, right in the middle.
I'm gonna run the rope all the way through here.
A straight line here.
That's what I'm thinking, right?
There's a way to tie a rope knot, right?
Yeah, there is.
I don't know.
Where do we tie it? This is our base.
This is important.
Pick a tree.
It's right here.
You have to use the middle one, because it's open.
It's open.
I'll check the function.
It's okay. It's okay.
Are you there? That's you.
Is it this high? If you're going to type it in anyway.
Maybe right here.
I'm almost there.
Is it enough? Long enough?
Enough?
The clouds are so thick.
These clouds are a foot long.
This guy's not cut out for this.
I'm gonna need you to roll that one up real tight first.
That's fine.
You don't get to see Jutaro do this very often.
I would never do that in private.
I've recently gotten into camping.
It seems so.
Jutaro doesn't like bugs and stuff.
He said he'd never go camping.
He said camping is good.
I don't see the point.
What's that?
Did you find it?
It's good, right?
Everything's fine, isn't it?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You want a picture of me struggling, right?
That's what I'm looking for.
I can do it.
Ugh! Bugs!
Oh, man.
He was like, "I can't do bugs.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
There's so many bugs in here.
What are we gonna do with this tree? No, we're just gonna have to try.
What can we do?
This is it.
It's too perfect.
One, two, three, four, five.
Stake it out or not.
I think we should stake it out.
Four stakes is fine, right? Uh, six stakes.
Just in case.
Two more boxes.
What's that? Is that it?
Is this real?
Why don't we just put these in the back?
Yes, they are.
I think I turned it the wrong way.
I can stick it in now.
It doesn't work!
I'll open it.
Let's make one this way.Let's make this one.
It's good, right?
It's good, right? Seriously.
Oh, this is almost right, isn't it? I'm pretty sure that's it.
Okay, look at this.
What?
It's perfect.
You've underestimated our survival skills.
You're taking it too far.
I'm going.
So far, so perfect.
Shall we go?
I'll just say, "Hello.
Say, "Hello.
And then, well, we can sleep together.
This one and this one.
That's right.
There you go.
Yes, perfect.
But there are ants in here.
Ax.
There's an ant nest.
Oh, there are so many.
Oh, wow.
To survive, part two.
Build a fire to watch over us from the wild.
Pray for a sword blade.
This is bad.
Because it's wet.
It's damp down there.
What?
Do you have any tools?
Here are the tools I prepared.
Hmm?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Weird stuff.
Lucene glasses and paper.
Rope.
Here we go.
Here, here, here.
This... this... this...
Here we go.
You can do this, can't you?
After everything you've prepared for us.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
But it'll take a while to make the fire.
Stay.
I'm from the mountains.
Oh, my God.
I can do it in 15 minutes.
Okay. Okay.
Here we go.
On this.
It's kind of like this.
Right here.
It's different from this.
I think it's like this.
I've never done this assembly before. I don't know what's going on.
Hey! That's great! What is it?
There's something on the ground!
There's a light!
Hey, go!
I hope it comes on.
It's all on this.
It's over!
You're all I've got!
It's all on you!
Kiichi, please!
You, please!
And here they are.
We used it together.
Well then...
Here.
It won't turn.
It's not going to turn.
I think he's squeezing it.
Maybe they're squeezing it too hard.
Oh!
Oh, that's weird.
Oh, that's disgusting.
What is this?
Ueyah!
There was a tree with mushrooms growing on it
How do you do that?
Oh, man, I don't know!
I'm telling you, I don't know!
What? You do it like this.
But if it doesn't turn, you know...
There's no friction, right?
That's right.
How do you get it to spin around?
Like this?
Like this, right?
Hold it like this.
You're all tangled up in this.
You're all tangled up in it.You're tangled up in it, you know that?
Try it this way... once.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Let's get this on.
What?
It's disgusting.
What the hell are you doing?
Ha-ha-ha.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Hey, what's this?
You know, every time I do this, I just...
You know, you should put some stuff around here.
You should see what I'm talking about.
Oh, wow.
What? Uh...
Uh...
Uh-oh.
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa.
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa.
Here we go.
Oh, I'll just be a minute.
I don't need that machine.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
This guy is the best
This guy is the strongest
I think I might have a use for this.
I'm gonna need you to bring it back.
I'd like that.
Dry wood.
I need some dry wood.
You got some dry wood?
I don't think so.
What is it?
What do you need?
Hey!
What?
Making a fire? What is that?
There you go.
Oh!
Greensence.
Ocracy.
From now on
Shikoku Toshio and other high school roads are the Ministry of Development's
Assistance for community hospital beds
They will meet
afternoon
How to assemble
Make sure the steel core is buried in the cutout.
The core should be buried in the cutout.
I'm missing a foot.
That's what's in the set, right?
What's the iron core for?
I don't know. It won't stay in.
Wow, that's great!
Hey, I found a really good one.
How did you find it?
How did you find that?
Golf balls.
Oh, my God, that guy's for real.
We're gonna have so much fun!
I want to eat you, too.
Hydration.
I'm going to try my hand at lifting.
Ten lifts and then I'm leaving.
If I can do 10, I can go home.
Yes, sir.
You're staying here for the rest of your life.
I think the world thinks I'm the one who's supposed to be playing.
It's not you.
It's not me.
I don't understand... what do these instructions mean?
What do you mean? You want to find another one?
No, I don't need another one.
Oh!
This is it.
That's it.
Is it done? I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Like this.
And this.
Is this one too?
It won't turn.
What's this?
Wait, isn't this how it's supposed to be?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's happening here?
How do you do it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Magnifying glass.
It's getting to this girl.
I'm gonna set him on fire.
Here we go.
That was a lot of fire back there.The fire must have been really hot back there.
No, it wasn't.
Well, I'd like one.
I think there's a string.
String?
Oh, I see.
You know, the kind where you cut up the string into little pieces.
Oh, that?
That's what that is.
Oh, that's what that is?
Yeah. Here.
There you go. There you go.
Oh, that's the sheet.
That's the sheet.
There it is!
Oh, here's a sheet!
This is it. This is it!
Here it comes!
Smoke.
You've got to do it for a minute.
Oh, smoke!
Nice!
This is it. It's really bad for the fire to go up.
I'm up for the challenge.
I'm trying.
I can't do it! I can't do this!
Try it one more time. It's too hard.
Chris, did you get it? It's definitely not the speed.
This is impossible, because we're going to keep going at the speed we're going.
That's why it's hard.
It was the speed.
Speed and pressure.
Definitely this picture
The end.
Oh?
I got it.
I think I got something.
Here, here, here.
Strong, strong, strong! Fire, fire, fire!
There it is, there it is, there it is.
Oh, oh!
Come on. Come on.
Isn't that a little fire?
Oh!
It's going out!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh!
Come on, come on, come on!
Here it comes!
Applause.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
This is not good.
Here it comes!
I've never seen that before in my life.
That's great!
Let's hear it!
Let's go! Let's go! Let me show you what I can do!
That's right.
Well, well, well... you can win now.
You can win.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, my God! The fire's stabilizing!
That's great! Wood is great!
Wood is good! I knew it!
The dryness is amazing!
Wow! It's so relaxing!
I love wood!
For the first time, I'm not relying on a lighter or anything like that.
It's the power of civilization.
Well, a magnifying glass is the power of civilization!
Yes, it is!
I'm having a hard time making a fire this big.
This is great!
It's amazing!
I'm a little attached to it! First time with fire!
I don't want this fire to die out!
I don't want it to die out!
It's awesome!
I feel so good right now!
It's not like I'm being punished!
It's like a thank you!
It's so good!
But fire is so good!
Fire is so good!
Next preview
This too?
Of course.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna steal your heart.
Ehhhh...Ehhhh...
I can't do it.
You're being too hard on me.
I really can't get out.
I really don't think I'm cut out for this.
I'm counting on you and Jin.
Can you think of any puns that would resonate with me?
Twelve minutes.
I'll tell you what I'm thinking of.
Keep me warm.
Finally... but it's like a penalty game.
I've never done that before.
I've never heard Jutran's voice like this before.